Guide to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Photographs, Part I: Negatives PHOTOS.023
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series I. Negatives, Bulk, 1940-1959; 1938-1969 (bulk 1940s-1950s)
  - Subseries I:I - Social, Cultural, Recreational and Educational Activities - 1938-1969
    - Chorus (con't), 1939-1962 (Negative 16920 - 16922; 16979; 29155; 17180 - 17183; 17745 - 17764; 17991 - 17993; 18174; 18226; 18627 - 18628; 20906 - 20911)
    - Christmas Party - Brown Team, Dec 20, 1961 (Negative 19596 - 19611)
    - Christmas Party: America Insignia, Dec 22, 1944 (Negative 2041 - 2044)
    - Christmas Party: Chemical and Paint Local, Dec 15, 1953 (Negative 12195)
    - Christmas Party: Open House, Dec 23, 1949 (Negative 5859 - 5862)
    - Christmas Party: Secretary Weaver of Department of Labor, undated (Negative 25233-25234)
    - Christmas: Activity around District 65 Center, Dec 11, 1956 (Negative 15593 - 15594)
    - Christmas: Parties; Tree; Open Houses at District 65; at Department Store Union and District 65; at District 65; Display; Ticket Sale; Christmas and Chanukah Party; Kiddie Parties; Cedar Rapids, Iowa Party; Charleston, Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America Party South Carolina; Cedar Rapids, Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America Local 110 Party, Iowa; Chanukkah Kiddie Party; Kiddie Party; Vice President Frank Brown's Team Party; Chanukkah at Finance Department; In Houston, Texas, Dec 24, 1942; Dec 1943; Dec 24, 1943; Dec 22, 1944; Dec 24, 1945; Dec 24, 1947; Dec 1948; Dec 7, 1948; 1951; Dec 22, 1951; Dec 20, 1952; Dec 30, 1952; Dec 31, 1952; Dec 22, 1953; Dec 24, 1953; Jan 15, 1954; Dec 19, 1959; Dec 1963; Dec 1964 (Negative 1328 -1333; 1583; 1589 -1591; 2045 -2047; 2432 2437; 2934 -2935; 3460 -3465; 4772 -4777; 4726; 8210; 8255 -8264; 10116 -10123; 10156 -10159; 10161 -10176; 12221 -12237; 12239 -12240; 12311 -12312; 17779 -17790; 18531; 22934 -22936; 23621 -23622)
    - Civil Rights: Conference in Washington, DC; Forum [Cleveland Robinson], Mar 1956; Feb 9, 1958 (Negative 14669 - 14679; 16349 - 16351)
    - Class Registration:Spring Education Program, Jan 19, 1961 (Negative 18606)
    - Class: Music Sight-Reading, Oct 25, 1960 (Negative 18481)
    - Class: Speech, May 20, 1961 (Negative 18950 - 18952)
    - Classes - Alumni Committee of 65 Classes, Aug 12, 1954 (Negative 13304)
    - Classes - Art: Tom Mooney Hall Association, undated; Jan 27, 1947; Nov 24, 1947; Feb 10, 1953; Apr 13, 1956; Oct 29, 1957; Nov 11, 1958; Apr 5, 1960; Oct 30, 1962; Apr 8, 1964 (Negative 25900 - 25904; 2953 - 2957; 3198; 9805; 14809 - 14810; 16250; 16912; 18024; 20895 - 20898; 23171)
    - Classes - Ballroom Dance: Ballroom Dancing: Modern Ballroom Dance Class, Oct 21, 1953; Dec 2, 1953; Oct 20, 1954; Nov 22, 1956 (Negative 11860 - 11861; 15510 - 15511; 12106 - 12107; 13433 - 13434)
    - Classes - Bookkeeping: Typing 1, Steno (First Day) [includes men], 1951; Sep 22, 1952; May 25, 1953; Sep 21, 1953; Feb 10, 1958; Oct 18, 1962; Nov 1, 1962 (Negative 7823 - 7824; 9447; 10898; 11690 - 11692; 16352; 20877 - 20880; 20912 - 20913)
    - Classes - Children's Class, Jan 27, 1948 (Negative 3506 - 3510)
    - Classes - Dance (I): Various; Tom Mooney Hall Association (includes children); at Local 1-S; Instructors Rita Hoffman and Tim Franklin; Teenage Dance Class; Teen Age Children of 65'ers; Graduation Party; Social; Students Thanksgiving Party; Party and Trophy Presentation; Graduation Exercise at Roseland; Graduations; Modern; Parties; Popular; Retired Members Dance Class, Nov 30, 1940; Mar 16, 1946; Feb 18, 1948; Nov 20, 1948; Jan 1949; Nov 25, 1949; Mar 27, 1950; Jan 1952; Oct 11, 1952; Mar 13, 1954; Sep 23, 1954; Oct 23, 1954; Jun 3, 1955; Nov 4, 1955; Dec 16, 1955; Mar 15, 1957 (Negative 255; 2539 - 2545; 3534 - 3536; 4680 - 4681; 4835 - 4836; 5777 - 5778; 6429; 8359 - 8362; 8407; 9549 - 9550; 12626 - 12628; 13399 - 13400; 13449; 14156 - 14157; 14424 - 14425; 14526 - 14527; 15836; 16258 - 16259; 17190 - 17191; 17731 - 17738)
    - Classes -Dance (II), Mar 20, 1959; Nov 23, 1959; Jun 14, 1960; Feb 10, 1961; Jun 16, 1961; Oct 27, 1961; Nov 24, 1961; Jan 12, 1962; Feb 2, 1962; Mar 29, 1962; Nov 2, 1962; 1951; Dec 1952; Jan 28, 1953; Apr 22, 1953; Oct 22, 1953; Feb 15, 1960 (Negative 18184 - 18189; 18764 - 18767; 19088 - 19091; 19446 - 19447; 19516 - 19518; 19650;19658 - 19660; 20007 - 20008; 20936 - 20937; 7653 - 7655; 10094 - 10095;9761 - 9762; 10667 - 10668; 11866 - 11867; 11652)
    - Classes - English: Classes for Spanish Speakers, Oct 10, 1949; Oct 27, 1961; 1961 (Negative 5620; 19448 - 19449; 19519)
    - Classes - First Aid: Red Cross First Aid Class, Jan 5, 1941; Feb 5, 1942; Apr 6, 1942 (Negative 887; 970; 1062)
    - Classes - General Office: Local Applicants Orientation Class, District 65; Typing Class, Sep 21, 1941; Jul 25, 1956 (Negative 14353; 15237 - 15240)
    - Classes - Guitar: Classes, Oct 22, 1953; Nov 13, 1958 (Negative 11870; 16930 - 16931)
    - Classes - Misc: Various; Journalism Class; Hebrew Class; Piano Class; Girls Applying For English-Spanish Class; Exercise Class, Mar 3, 1947; Feb 25, 1954; Jan 17, 1955; Apr 8, 1958; Nov 11, 1958; Sep 12, 1962; Mar 29, 1965 (Negative 3011; 12553; 13732; 16492;16913; 20460 - 20461; 23641)
    - Classes - Photography, 1950; Mar 16, 1951; Feb 20, 1958 (Negative 6389 - 6390; 16374; 7666)
    - Classes - Receptionists' Class, Aug 17, 1942 (Negative 1228)
    - Classes - Stenography, Nov 25, 1940; Jul 23, 1951; May 6, 1952; Sep 9, 1952; Sep 23, 1952 (Negative 29668; 7788; 8757; 9395; 9451 - 9452)
    - Classes - Typing: Various; Graduation, Apr 25, 1951; 1952; Sep 22, 1952; Mar 2, 1953; May 5, 1953; Nov 17, 1953; Apr 1, 1954; Sep 20, 1954; Feb 20, 1956; Oct 2, 1956; Nov 18, 1957; Oct 29, 1958; Mar 10, 1959; Oct 24, 1960; Oct 22, 1962 (Negative 7751; 9195 - 9197; 9444 - 9446; 10258 - 10259; 10715; 12015 - 12016; 12749; 13387 - 13388; 14636 - 14637; 15427 - 15428; 16270; 16807 - 16808; 17172 - 17173; 18468 - 18469; 20873 - 20876)
    - Classes -Trade Union Class: Various; Graduations; Seminar, 1939; 1940; Apr 3, 1940; Mar 13, 1940; May 22, 1940; Feb 1, 1941; May 10, 1941; Nov 8, 1941; Jan 22, 1945; Feb 1, 1958 (Negative 7; 29700 - 29701; 29672; 29675; 29687; 497; 678; 806; 2065; 16334 - 16451)
    - Classes: New Members, Nov 1, 1950 (Negative 7293)
    - Classes: Various; Graduations; Assignment; Committee; Graduation Parties; Registration; English For Spanish Speaking Members - Seven From Vita Foods; Graduates; Rank and File Teachers Portraits [Portrait Feature]; On Use Of Proper Government Agencies Conducted By Security Plan; Graduates Celebrate (Negative 1373; 6155 -6158; 8347 -8350; 8207; 8244; 9800; 9806; 10295 -10296; 11586; 12329 -12333; 29031; 12460; 13142 -13144; 13378; 13690)
    - Classes (con't), 1943-1946 (Negative 14206 -14207; 15183 -15186; 16322; 29106; 16499;16560 -16569; 17043 -17045; 18941 -18946; 19349 -19354; 19545 -19549; 19651)
    - Club 65: Members Watch Television around the Bar; Band; Shower; Wedding Reception; Jewish Night; VJ [Victory over Japan] Celebration; Schranz and Bieber Dines; Food Preparation; Bernkoff and Manel; Yugoslav Partisan Dines; Progressive Novelty Strikers Birthday Party; Informal Table Scene; Construction; Mural for club with Artist Stan Glaubach; Supper Club (Including Opening Night); Sterns: Stewards at Club 65 Before Council Meeting1; London Gramo. Workers Celebrate Lynne Aronowitz Birthday At Club 65; Local 2 Night; Metropolitan News Victory Dinner; Publicity for Sweet 16 Party; Irish Night; Friday Night Waitress Service; Showtable; Celebrates Fourth Anniversary; Retiring Irving Reuben of Club 65; Exchange Teachers Tour and Lunch; Shoe Market Leaders, 1944-1961 (Negative 4032; 4040 - 4041; 2064; 1927; 1935 - 1937; 1956 - 1963; 2248 - 2250; 2490; 2572 - 2579; 2698 - 2699; 2700 - 2701; 3144; 7517; 9833 - 9835)
    - Club 65 (con't), 1944-1961 (Negative 10308 - 10309; 10556 - 10562; 10572; 10600 - 10614; 10637; 10638; 10691 - 10699; 10707; 11425; 11093 - 11101; 11875; 12198; 14420 - 14421; 15832 - 15834; 15840; 16079; 19319)
    - Cluff Dance, Aug 19, 1943 (Negative 1515 - 1518)
    - Cohen, C. 80th Birthday, Mar 12, 1948 (Negative 29559 - 29562)
    - Cohen, Jack of Arthur Bier - Retirement Party, Feb 28, 1961 (Negative 18752 - 18753)
    - Cohen, Louis, First Draftee [Koren War] [Portrait Feature], Aug 29, 1950 (Negative 28722)
    - Cohn Hall Marx v. Garment Support Game, Apr 21, 1945 (Negative-number 2148 - 2149)
    - Community Cabaret Rehearsal of "The Malady Lingers On" Sponsored by Medical Plan, Jan 1, 1955 (Negative 13693 - 13707)
    - Community Class Party, Jun 20, 1958 (Negative 16604 - 16605)
    - Community Committee Trip to Hyde Park, Washington Heights Committee, May 2, 1954 (Negative 12883 - 12884)
    - Community Fund Drive Beneficiaries - Jewish Organizations Collect, Oct 29, 1958 (Negative 16805 - 16806)
    - Community Meeting H.I.P., West Bronx, Jun 20, 1952 (Negative 9074 - 9083)
    - Community Party of Hempstead Committee Group at Sol Molofsky's House, Jul 5, 1953 (Negative 11232 - 11268)
    - Community Social Zones 26, 27g, May 22, 1954 (Negative 12928)
    - Coney Island Feature, Jul 21, 1951 (Negative 7832 - 7853)
    - Connie Bryant's Gym, 1968 (Negative 24516 - 24541)
    - Consumer Service: Committee Comparison Shoppers; Holiday Children's Party; Christmas, Apr 28, 1955; Nov 30, 1957; Dec 10, 1960 (Negative 14038; 16281 - 16282; 18542 - 18544)
    - Convention, Sep 17, 1965 - Sep 19, 1965 (Negative 24144 - 24180)
    - Co-op Education Guild of New York, Sep 29, 1956 (Negative 15360)
    - Corrugated: Workers Signing for Training Programs; Graduation; Higher Horizons Planning Committee; Machinery Being Hoisted into District 65 Headquarters Building [to be Used in a Class to Train Members?] and On 9th Floor of the Building; Machinery [with Workers] At Workplace; Training - Party Including Employers; New Year's Party; Social; Nightclub [Division]; Trophy Award Winners; Class Studies Incentive Plans; Dinner Honoring 25-year Men; Spanish-Speaking Members; Retirement Party for Ralph Yearwood and Le Roy De Veaux; Math Class, undated; Jan 1, 1944; Apr 27, 1946; Apr 7, 1951; Dec 6, 1952; Oct 22, 1956; Jan 24, 1957; Feb 9, 1957; Mar 5, 1959; Dec 1967; Aug 6, 1969 (Negative 25511 - 25512; 25515 - 25517; 25595 - 25597; 25598 - 25608; 25767 - 25770; 25609 - 25612; 25754 - 25755)
    - Corrugated (con't), 1944-1969 (Negative 1598 - 1599; 2615 - 2616; 7717 - 7719; 10058 - 10063; 15492; 15634 - 15635; 15664; 17165; 25065; 25746 - 25748)
    - Creative Print: Printmakers Christmas Party; Class Shop, Dec 22, 1944; May 15, 1945 (Negative 2048 - 2049; 2164)
    - Credit Union: Party; Committee Retirement Party for Ben Banks; Dinner Executive Board and Depositors, 1961; Jun 21, 1962; Jan 1968 (Negative 19307; 20234 - 20235; 24307 - 24323)
    - Crown Novelty Party, Jan 28, 1942 (Negative 953)
    - Current Events Class, Oct 5, 1944 (Negative 1949)
    - Dade City, Florida, Sep 22, 1952 (Negative 9432 - 9436)
    - Daily Noose [Newspaper Parody]: Various; Skit; Scene, Jan 10, 1946; Jan 23, 1946; Jul 6, 1948 (Negative 2462; 2472; 4357 - 4365)
    - Dalton School Girls Visit District 65, Apr 9, 1945 (Negative 2139)
    - Dance Exhibit at Knitwear Meeting - Kesslers Doing Mambo, Jun 19, 1961 (Negative 19082)
    - Dance to Celebrate Lillian Upshur's Election as Co-Leader of Harlem District, Dec 18, 1959 (Negative 17791)
    - Dance: Ninth Annual, Feb 28, 1942; Mar 14, 1942 (Negative 988 - 1007; 3236 - 3236; 1027 - 1033)
    - Dance: Processing Local, Feb 15, 1957 (Negative 15753 - 15756)
    - Dances: Optical Division, Oct 26, 1943; Nov 11, 1943 (Negative 1555 - 1557; 1573)
    - Daran, Esther Farewell Party, Sep 20, 1957 (Negative 16123 - 16124)
    - Darkroom, District 65, Nov 23, 1940 (Negative 29702 - 29705)
    - Death of a Salesman Rehearsal, Mar 24, 1954 (Negative 12713 - 12714)
    - Delegations: from Honduras; from Cuba; from Iceland; of Girl Scouts,Tour 65, May 18, 1955; Jun 14, 1955; Sep 20, 1955; Oct 21, 1955 (Negative 14123 - 14128; 14166 - 14172; 14346 - 14349; 14408)
    - Dental Meeting Demonstration of Denture Technique, Sep 25, 1962 (Negative 20519)
    - Department Store Workers Union [probably Local 1250] Celebrations, 1940s; Gym Night; Exteriors Macy's's, Bloomingdale's's, Stern's, Saks, Namms, Loeser's, Hearn's; Christmas Party, Local 3; Victory Dance; Victory Celebration; Dance, 1940; Mar 6, 1946; 1951; Dec 24, 1951; Sep 22, 1952; Oct 18, 1952; Jun 21, 1958 (Negative 30002 - 30022; 30026 - 30028; 2525 - 2526; 7533 - 7542; 8265 - 8266; 9430 - 9431; 9564 - 9568; 16609 - 16615)
    - Department Store: (Performance Skit? at a Meeting), 1940 (Negative 30039; 30054 - 30057; 30072)
    - Direct Mail: Inserting and Zoning Class; Local Gets Grads of Union Inserting Class; Local Starts Blood Bank, Apr 28, 1958; Mar 3, 1959; Dec 14, 1959 (Negative 16532 - 16536; 17148 - 17149; 17774)
    - Directory Publishers Newly Organized, Nov 30, 1959 (Negative 17765)
    - Display Local:144 - Dance [probably 12/1949]; Banquets; Ben Berman Receives Scroll; Anniversary, Dec 1949; Mar 27, 1954; Apr 3, 1955; May 25, 1957; May 2, 1959 (Negative 5836 - 5837; 12716 - 12721; 14053 - 14054; 15958 - 15960; 17279 - 17282)
    - Distributive Workers Union Basketball Game and Dance, Mar 31, 1950 (Negative 6513 - 6522)
    - Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America, 3rd Anniversary, Suffolk Virginia, Jul 17, 1953 (Negative 11359 - 11370)
    - Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America, Books for Charleston Library, Dec 30, 1953 (Negative 12257)
    - Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America, Convention Nightclub, Oct 5, 1950 - Oct 7, 1950 (Negative 7189 - 7197)
    - Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America, National Convention Green Room, Apr 10, 1953 - Apr 12, 1953 (Negative 10338 - 10357)
    - Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America, Suffolk, Local 26, Virginia Anniversary Party, Jun 28, 1952 (Negative 9117 - 9142)
    - Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America, Typing Class, Chicago, Illinois, Mar 17, 1953 (Negative 10314 - 10315)
    - Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America; 194 Bowling League Play, Chicago, Illinois, Oct 28, 1953 (Negative 11902 - 11904)
    - District 65 10th Annual Dance (includes African American Members), Mar 16, 1943 (Negative 1393 - 1396)
    - District 65 Book Shop, Aug 9, 1945 (Negative 2241)
    - District 65 Committee, Jun 1944 (Negative 1792 - 1793)
    - District 65 Convention, 1952, Atlantic City, May 17, 1952 - May 18, 1952 (Negative 8877)
    - District 65 Convention, 1956, May 11, 1956 - May 13, 1956 (Negative 15032 - 15039; 15065 - 15069; 15142)
    - District 65 Nightclub (I): Various; Trineers (Entertainment); Opening; Portraits (includes Shots with Harry Belafonte); Nightclub Committees At Work; Shots Including Sam Levenson and other Performers, Nightclub Workers such as Cigarette Vendors, and Interracial Couples); Cast of Bloomer Girl; Shots with Morris Doswell; North Atlantic Nightclub Show; 10,000th Customer; The Mikado At; Entertainment; Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America, Convention Nightclub; Engagement Party; Mr. and Mrs. Skoras Story; Elsie Andrews Dance Group and Portrait of Elsie; Corrugated [Division]; Screen Publicists Party; Garment Center Stewards at Arthur Osman's Birthday; Auditions; Bridges, Harry; Band and Jesse Torres; Entertainer-Unidentified [Portrait Feature]; Entertainers (includes shots of Luther Thomas, Nightclub Singer) [Portrait Feature]; St. Patrick's Day; Reuben Lugo, Nightclub Singer [Portrait Feature]; Stars, The Mello Tones; Medical Plan Community, 1947-1953 (Negative 3205; 5704 - 5705; 27000; 5520; 5549 - 5559; 5549 - 5559; 5560 - 5618; 5628 -5642; 25908 - 25929; 5594 - 5609; 5628 - 5642; 5734; 5739; 25930 -25939; 25941-25974; 26047 - 26048; 25952 - 25962; 25981 - 26002; 6646 - 6657; 6060 - 6062)
    - District 65 Nightclub (II), 1947-1953 (Negative 6077 - 6083; 6126; 26003 - 26010; 26025; 6116 - 6124; 6331; 26026 - 26040; 6327 - 6331; 6533 - 6536; 26041 - 26046; 6597 - 6601; 7197; 7273 - 7283; 7189 - 7197; 7298; 7309 - 7317; 7369 - 7372; 7965 - 7967;7646; 7717; 7719; 7644 - 7646; 7717 - 7719)
    - District 65 Nightclub (III), Mar, 1950; Mar 15, 1950; May 6, 1950; Oct 1950; Oct 5, 1950; Nov 4, 1950; Nov 11, 1950; Dec 2, 1950; 1951; Mar 10, 1951 (Negative 7965 - 7967;7646; 7717; 7719; 7644 - 7646; 7717 - 7719; 7733 - 7739; 7739; 7903 - 7910; 8220 - 8225; 8472 - 8476; 8485; 8408 -8412)
    - District Nightclub (IV), Aug 29, 1951; Dec 8, 1951; 1952; Jan 19, 1952; Feb 14, 1952; Feb 19, 1952; Mar 15, 1952; Feb 24, 1953; Mar 10, 1953; Oct 17, 1953 (Negative 28815; 29844; 29846 - 29847; 29849; 28819 - 28820; 29843 - 29848; 8551 - 8558; 28820; 29843; 29845; 29848; 28945; 10290; 11827 - 11843)
    - District 65 Optometrist, 1961 (Negative 19553)
    - District 65 Pharmacy House Vitamins, Oct 3, 1957 (Negative 16268 - 16269)
    - District 65 Supper Club (Including Opening Night); Local 2 Night, Mar 28, 1953; Apr 25, 1953 (Negative 10556 - 10562; 10572; 10600 - 10614; 10691 - 10699)
    - District 65 Visitors: Dalton School Girls Visit; Brazilian Trade Unionists Visit 65 [C. Robinson]; British Visitor, Cyril Hammett, Editor of Dawn Magazine [David Livingston]; Tour of District 65 Center by Hunter College Students; Canadian Visitor to 65, Jim Mason, of Vancouver Local 535 R.W.D.S.U.; R.W.D.S.U. General Council Members; Touring Labor, Public and Employer Group From Pakistan; Visiting Kenya Official; Visitors from Tanzania; Chilean Visitors Tour 65; Bolivian Visitor at 65, Apr 9, 1945; Aug 3, 1954; Oct 2, 1954; Dec 16, 1957; Jun 10, 1959; Jun 19, 1959; Oct 6, 1959; Oct 23, 1959; Aug 24, 1962; Jun 1963; Mar 2, 1965 (Negative 2139; 13407; 13266 - 13268; 16302; 17384 - 17387; 17388; 17702; 20407 - 20409; 23803 - 23811; 17659; 21888 - 21889)
    - District 65: Grand Opening of Union Pharmacy, Apr 12, 1952 (Negative 8671 - 8673)
    - Doswell's Wedding Reception at 65, Feb 21, 1947 (Negative 3008)
    - Drama 417 Company, Dec 9, 1953 (Negative 12185)
    - Drama Group Rehearsal - Various Rehearsals; Plant in the Sun; This'll Kill Ya; The Malady Lingers On; In conjunction with Village News Staff; Deep Are The Roots, Aug 1939; Oct 17, 1945; Jan 7, 1946; Jan 7, 1948; Sep 1, 1948; Sep 21, 1953; Dec 19, 1951; Oct 12, 1953; Oct 20, 1954; Apr 15, 1958; Nov 12, 1958; Feb 5, 1959 (Negative 8; 2354; 2455; 3495; 4468-4469; 11689; 8251-8252; 11805-11810; 13435; 16500; 16915-16919; 17096)
    - Drama Group - Social; Nardowitz; Painting Sets; Audience; Executive Meeting; Negro History Play; Show; Performing at Member Meeting; Drama Speech Group; Opens with Deep Are The Roots; Discusses one act plays; Dramatics; Drama Group Director of Death of a Salesman ["Portrait" feature], Feb 1940; Nov 23, 1940; Oct 1942; Apr 28, 1948; Nov 20, 1951; Feb 2, 1953; Nov 21, 1952; Nov 23, 1953; Jul 27, 1955; Feb 25, 1959; Apr 1, 1959; Undated; Mar 11, 1954 (Negative 115; 238; 1316; 4042-4043; 8199; 9781; 9976-9983; 12055-12056; 14255; 17175-17176; 17203; 29633; 29677-29685; 29856)
    - Drama Group - Various, Aug 20, 1942; 1948; Jun 13, 1949; Aug 4, 1952; Sep 15, 1952; Dec 17, 1952; Jun 3, 1953; Jul 15, 1953; Oct 28, 1953; Dec 28, 1953; Jan 27, 1954; Jun 20, 1958 (Negative 1235-1236; 4407; 5206-5207; 9281-9284; 9419; 10096; 11057; 11314-11315; 11886; 12244; 12371-12372; 16606-16608)
    - Drama: New Theatre League, Labor Drama Tournament, 1940 Plaque, Apr 19, 1940 (Negative 64)
    - Drug Local 1199: Gets 65 Basketball Award from Arthur Osman; Negro History Celebration [Shots including Sidney Poitier], Apr 28, 1954; Feb 28, 1960 (Negative 12853; 17976 - 17986)
    - Dry Goods: Outside Salesman First Annual [Celebration]; Banquet Committee; Banquet; Outside Salesmen Fourth Annual United Jewish Appeal Banquet; Meeting Hears Dr. Wittenberg on Cause and Prevention of Heart Disease, Feb 2, 1946; Jan 27, 1954; Jan 30, 1954; Mar 12, 1955; Nov 23, 1959 (Negative 2486; 12373; 12383 - 12391; 13961 - 13963; 17739 - 17740)
    - East Bronx: Baseball; Socials; Medical Group Exam, May 7, 1941; Sep 20, 1941; Oct 18, 1941; 1952 (Negative 1750 - 1751; 766 - 769; 791; 9408 - 9413)
    - East Harlem Community Meetings, May 21, 1954; Feb 10, 1955 (Negative 12925 - 12927; 13824 - 13827)
    - East Side Canteen, Jun 11, 1943 (Negative 1497 - 1499)
    - Education Department: Signs Direct Mail Members or Vocational Courses; Meets Textile Members on Vocational Training Program, Jan 18, 1960; Jan 26, 1960 (Negative 17806 - 17815; 17820)
    - Education Program: Graduation; Classes In Session; Classes in Typing, Music, Spanish; Vocational Courses, Textile Members First Class [Frank Brown]; Classes and Teachers, 2/9-10-11/61; Registration for Classes, May 1, 1956; Oct 14, 1959; Oct 27, 1959; Mar 1, 1960, Feb 1961; Jan 1964 (Negative 17283 - 17284; 17676 - 17681; 17703 - 17706; 17987; 18645 - 18664; 23000 - 23002)
    - Egal, Sam (left), and John O'Neil (right)] [Portrait Feature], Oct 2, 1950 (Negative 28732 - 28732)
    - Eggleston, Louis [Portrait Feature], Aug 1959 (Negative 29178 - 29179)
    - Egres, Marie of District 76 Visiting 65 Delegate to Conventions of Jehovah's Witnesses at Yankee Stadium, Jul 24, 1953 (Negative 11386)
    - Election Social ["Our goal 2500 members organized…"], Jan 1940 (Negative 13591 - 13593)
    - Ellington, Duke, Interview at Cafe Society, Jan 26, 1956 (Negative 14593 - 14601)
    - Elliot, James, Retired 65er Who Wrote Memoirs [Portrait Feature], Aug 16, 1951 (Negative-number 28768)
    - Engagement Party in Saturday Nightclub, Nov 4, 1950 (Negative 7298)
    - Engbarth, Marie - Teaching Office Machines, undated (Negative 24472 - 24477)
    - Entertainment, undated (Negative 184 - 185)
    - Entertainment: Midtown Area Membership Meeting, Jul 1949 (Negative 5326 - 5329)
    - Entry Job Training Graduation Including Guests from Police Department, Feb 1968 (Negative 24956 - 24959)
    - European Trade Unionists Tour 65 Center, Mar 14, 1958 (Negative 16429 - 16431)
    - Everlast - Labor Unity Party, Sep 26, 1961 (Negative 19312 - 19313)
    - Exchange Teachers Tour 65; Lunch at Club 65, Aug 9, 1957 (Negative 16079)
    - Exhibition of Ceramics at Home - Lilo Nelson, Bloomingdale's Worker., Nov 1967 (Negative 25110 - 25112)
    - Farewell Dinner for Julio Reyes, Jul 9, 1965 (Negative 23727 - 23729)
    - Farewell Party for Bob Rogow, Aug 1964 (Negative 23340 - 23341)
    - Farewell Party for Klaber Brothers, Oct 8, 1951 (Negative 7995)
    - Farewell Party for Mort Lewert, Sep 14, 1962 (Negative 20496 - 20499; 20766)
    - Farewell Party for Pete Stein, Feb 19, 1944 (Negative 29514 - 29515)
    - Farewell Party for Phil Goodman, Jul 21, 1945 (Negative 2223)
    - Farewell Party Given by A. Hirsch Workers for Harry Bloom, Oct 21, 1955 (Negative 14409)
    - Farmer, Labor, Consumer, Picnic - Lakewood, New Jersey, Aug 11, 1951 (Negative 7864 - 7879)
    - FBI Basketball Game, Jan 8, 1953 (Negative 9678)
    - Feller, Bunny, and Henry Turin (Members of Macy's Local 1-S), Marriage, Nov 7, 1941 (Negative 4625 - 4633)
    - Finland Forum, Feb 27, 1940 (Negative 19423)
    - First Chorus Rehearsal, Jan 24, 1946 (Negative 2475)
    - First Downtown Social, Sep 6, 1941 (Negative 749 - 752)
    - First Drama Rehearsal, Oct 10, 1945 (Negative 2339 - 2340)
    - First Recreation Director Meeting, Oct 2, 1945 (Negative 2317)
    - Flu Injections Given 65 Staff, Oct 17, 1957 (Negative 16159 - 16160)
    - Food Local: Spanish Membership Meeting; Social, Dec 16, 1953; Dec 12, 1957 (Negative 12205; 16296 - 16297)
    - Foster, Jack - Tribute, Sep 27, 1961 (Negative 19310 - 19311)
    - Frank, Herb - Retirement Party, Jan 1969 (Negative 25621 - 25625)